the12volt.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy Policy

|   
  | Mobile Electronics Basics  
---  
Car Audio & Mobile Video  
Car Security & Convenience  
Cruise Controls  
Forums  
General Information  
Et Cetera  

  |  |    

**the12volt.com respects your privacy. This statement discloses the privacy practices for both our web site and e-mail system.**

| 

Privacy Statement   
  
---  
the12volt.com endeavors to maintain the strictest professional standards in all transactions with our visitors. This standard of conduct includes maintaining the visitor's confidentiality.

Personal information is held in the strictest confidence and will not be sold, divulged or otherwise revealed to any individual or entity without your express permission. This includes any information of a personal or private nature you have shared with us.

the12volt.com will cooperate to the extent required by law with any law enforcement agency upon presentation of properly executed and served subpoenas or warrants.

We have designed the12volt.com so that no personal identifying information is displayed online or is accessible to the general public. We do not reveal your e-mail address or other personal information, except to you when you update your profile information. We do not sell or rent our visitor or member information to any outside party under any circumstances.  

Solicited Information  
  
---  
We do not sell, rent, or share your information to any outside parties under any circumstances.  

Use of Your E-mail Address  
  
---  
When you join our forums, make an entry in our guestbook, or submit an installer entry, an email is automatically sent to you. If you are a forum member and have email notification enabled or you are watching any forums or forum topics for replies, an email will be sent to you. You may always un-watch topics and forums by clicking on the appropriate link in the respective area near the bottom of the page. Instructions are also included in each of these emails you receive. If you change your email address in your forum profile, an email will be sent to you to reactivate your membership. If you wish to be removed from our forums, you may do so by sending an email to: [deleteMember@the12volt.com](mailto:deleteMember@the12volt.com).   

Cookies  
  
---  
the12volt.com uses software tags called "cookies" to save information for our users when completing forms and/or logging into our forums. The information we collect with cookies is not sold, rented or shared with any outside parties under any circumstances. 

Third party advertisers may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or web beacons to collect information, in the course of displaying ads on this site. For your options on handling cookies, please see your browser's help file. 

**Google and the[DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx):**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).   

|    

| Search the12volt.com  
---  
  
Custom Search   

Send [this page](mailto:?SUBJECT=Take%20a%20look%20at%20this%20web%20page%20I%20found%2C%20Privacy%20Policy&BODY=You%20can%20see%20it%20here%3A%20https%3A//web.archive.org/web/20101231134208id_/http%253A//www.the12volt.com/privacy/privacy.asp "Send this page to a friend") to a friend.  
---  
Friday, December 31, 2010 | • | Copyright © 1999-2010 the12volt.com | • | [Donate to the12volt.com](https://www.paypal.com/xclick/business=the12volt%40the12volt.com&item_name=Donate+to+the12volt.com&no_note=1&tax=0&currency_code=USD "Make a donation to the12volt.com") | • | [Privacy Policy](http://www.the12volt.com/privacy/privacy.asp) | • | [Advertising](http://www.the12volt.com/adv/default.asp)
